<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    // Generics
    <string name="gen_next">Next</string>
    <string name="gen_finished">Finished</string>

    // Login Activity
    <string name="login_title">Login Lloyds Student</string>

    // First Time Setup
    <string name="first_title">Lloyds Student Setup</string>
    <string name="first_intro">Welcome to Lloyds Student your all-in-one finance solution during Uni
                               ! \n\nIn order to set up your Lloyds Student App we need to take a few
                               details to link your bank account with the app and get you started</string>
    <string name="first_label_1">1. Online Banking User ID</string>
    <string name="first_label_2">2. Online Banking Password</string>
    <string name="first_passcode_info">Next we need you to set-up a four digit passcode which you\'ll
                                       use each time you log into the app to keep your details
                                       secure try to make your passcode memorable but also
                                       unique and secure</string>
    <string name="first_passcode_label">Passcode:</string>
    <string name="first_passcode_confirm">Confirm:</string>
    <string name="first_failed_login">Sorry but your online login details didn\'t match our records (Make sure you\'re using your Online Banking Login)</string>
    <string name="first_failed_passcode">Sorry but your inputs didn\'t match. Please try again making sure you enter both passcodes the same</string>

    // Budget Activity
    <string name="budget_my_budget">My Weekly Budget Is\u00A0</string>
    <string name="budget_you_spent">You\'ve spent</string>
    <string name="budget_thank">less than last week</string>
    <string name="budget_remaining_start">You\'ve got\u00A0\u00A0</string>
    <string name="budget_remaining_end">\u00A0 left this week</string>
    <string name="budget_cash_button">Add Cash Entry</string>
    <string name="budget_settings_button">Budget Settings</string>

    // Chart Titles
    <string name="budget_pie_title">Where You\'re Spending</string>
    <string name="budget_line_title">Weekly Spend</string>
    <string name="budget_overview">Weekly Overview</string>
    <string name="login_intro">Welcome to Lloyds Student. \n\nPlease enter your 4 digit pass code to Login and View your account</string>

    // Cash Entry
    <string name="cash_title">Cash Purchase</string>
    <string name="cash_description">Use this dialouge to log any cash purchases you\'ve made so your budgeting advice can be as accurate as possible ! If you don\'t log your cash purchases then the ATM transactions will just show up in the Misc category of your budgeting</string>
    <string name="cash_name">Purchase Name</string>
    <string name="cash_category">Category</string>
    <string name="cash_amount">Amount</string>
    <string name="cash_balance">Balance</string>
    <string name="cash_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cash_add">Add</string>
    <string name="cash_category_prompt">Choose a country</string>
    <string-array name="cash_categories">
        <item>Food</item>
        <item>Travel</item>
        <item>Beauty &amp; Hygiene</item>
        <item>Entertainment</item>
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Clothes</item>
        <item>Leisure</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="app_name">Lloyds Student</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello World</string>
    <string name="menu_login">Menu Login</string>
    <string name="menu_main">Menu Main</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Action Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Activity Login</string>
    <string name="customerName">Mike Williams</string>
    <string name="lastLogin">LAST LOGIN 11:56 NEWCASTLE</string>
    <string name="accountType">Student Account</string>
    <string name="currentMoney">£2000.00</string>
    <string name="accountDetails">20-14-19 | 12345678</string>
    <string name="makeTransferButton">Make a Transfer</string>
    <string name="payContactButton">Pay a Contact</string>
    <string name="main_title">Homepage</string>
    <string name="spaceinbetweenthebuttons"></string>
    <string name="accountTypeInfo">Account Overview</string>
    <string name="balanceAvailable">Balance</string>
    <string name="interestRateText">Interest Rate</string>
    <string name="overdraftText">Overdraft Limit</string>
    <string name="interestRate">0.5%</string>
    <string name="overdraftLimit">£1500.00</string>
    <string name="title_activity_first_time">FirstTime</string>
    <string name="lastmonth">Last Month</string>
    <string name="thismonth">This Month</string>
    <string name="transactiondate1">29th August</string>
    <string name="transactionstorename1">Amazon EU</string>
    <string name="transactioncost1">-£12.99</string>
    <string name="transactiondate2">29th August</string>
    <string name="transactionstorename2">T.K MAXX</string>
    <string name="transactioncost2">-£52.99</string>
    <string name="transactiondate3">24th August</string>
    <string name="transactionstorename3">WWW.CASH.COM</string>
    <string name="transactioncost3">+£82.51</string>
    <string name="transactiondate4">19th August</string>
    <string name="transactionstorename4">Cash Withdrawal</string>
    <string name="transactioncost4">-£100.00</string>
    <string name="AlertTitle">Don\'t Recognise This ?</string>
    <string name="CallUsButton">Proceed</string>
    <string name="CallUsButtonCancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="AlertMessage">If you don\'t recognise this payment/transfer we might need to take some action. To keep your money safe we need you to call our Fraud
    Team or fill a case online right now and it will be dealt with one of our staffs right away to investigate this transaction. </string>
    <string name="makeatransfertitle">Transfer money between your Lloyd\'s accounts</string>
    <string name="makeatransferfrom">From:</string>
    <string name="makeatransferto">To:</string>

    <string-array name="accounts">
        <item>Current Account</item>
        <item>Savings Account</item>
        <item>Joined Account</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="paycontacttitle">Enter the account details of the person you want to pay</string>
    <string name="paycontactlimitandinfo">(Limit: Minimum £1, Maximum daily: £300)</string>
    <string name="horsepointerHomeTitle">Home</string>
    <string name="horsepointerHomeMessage">Banking should always be as safe as possible. We use the latest online security measures to protect your money, your personal information and your privacy.
    We guarantee to refund your money in the unlikely event you experience fraud with our Internet Banking service - as long as you\'ve been careful,
        for example, by taking reasonable steps to keep your security information safe. We protect you with safeguards that meet Industry Standards.
    Lloyds Bank plc is authorised by the Prudential Regulation Authority and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority and the Prudential Regulation Authority under registration number 119278. Authorisation can be checked on the Financial Services Register at www.fca.org.uk. Lloyds Bank plc are members of the
        Financial Services Compensation Scheme and the Financial Ombudsman Service. We subscribe to the Lending Code;
        copies of the Code can be obtained from www.lendingstandardsboard.org.uk.</string>
    <string name="transfermoneytitle">Transfer money between your accounts</string>
    <string name="confirmdetails">Confirm your transaction details</string>
    <string name="amount">Amount</string>
    <string name="reference">Payment Reference</string>
    <string name="payacontacttitle">Pay a Contact</string>
    <string name="red_string">Red</string>
    <string name="green_string">Green</string>
    <string name="yellow_string">Yellow</string>

    <string-array name="helpmenu">
        <item>Account Management</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
        <item>Budget Notification</item>
        <item>Lloyd\'s Banking Tour </item>
        <item>Contact Us</item>
        <item>Other Products</item>
        <item>Terms and Conditions</item>
        <item>FAQs</item>
        <item>Send feedback</item>
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Log Out</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="LogOutTitle">Log Out</string>
    <string name="LogOutMessage">Are you sure you want to Quit ?</string>
    <string name="LogOutPositive">Yes</string>
    <string name="LogOutNegative">No</string>
    <string name="ContactUsMessage">If you have any query regarding your online banking or report a card lost or stolen then you can use one of the below options. </string>
    <string name="ContactUsEmail">Email</string>
    <string name="ContactUsPhone">Call Us</string>
    <string name="ContactUsLiveChat">Live Chat</string>
    <string name="ContactUsTitle">Call the helpline</string>
    <string name="ContactUsDialogMessage">Your call may be recorded for training or monitoring purposes. Call charges applies, Please check with your local provider for more information.</string>
    <string name="ContactUsCancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ContactUsCall">Call</string>
    <string name="ContactUsEmalTitle">Email</string>
    <string name="ContactUsEmalMessage">This will take you into an email app. We will respond back to you within 2 working days. </string>
    <string name="ContactUsEmalCancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ContactUsEmalOk">Email</string>
    <string name="FeedbackMessage">We greatly value your feedback to help us maintain our current features. You could make a real difference to our service and it
    would really help us understand what we have to do in order to give a better service to our customer\'s. </string>
    <string name="FeedbackSubmit">Submit</string>
    <string name="LloydsTourTitle">Welcome to your Lloyds Banking Tour</string>
    <string name="LloydsTourmessage">We will go though each aspect of the Lloyds Mobile Banking Application. \nSwipe to find out more.</string>
    <string name="LloydsTourPageTwomessage">You can switch between tabs easily with a touch of a button. There are three buttons at the top of the screen which will take you to different
    aspect of the Lloyds Banking App. </string>
    <string name="LloydsTour7Message">You are ready to try the app for yourself. Feel free to come again and go through these tour to familiarise your self with what Lloyds Banking Group offers. </string>
    <string name="LloydsTour3Message">Swipe to the right of the screen to access the Help Menu. Here you will find all the necessary settings and functions which are associated with Lloyds Banking Group.</string>
    <string name="LloydsTour4Message">Manage and access your money instantly. With the help of Lloyds Banking App, you get to view your account balance, transactions and also get to switch between other accounts.  </string>
    <string name="LloydsTour5Message">Fraud Detection feature in place to keep your money safe. If you don\'t recognise a transaction on your Account Overview, you can report it straightaway
    to our Fraud Team with a touch of a button. </string>
    <string name="LloydsTour6Message">Now it\'s been made easier for you to transfer money to a payee with using our Lloyds Banking App. Transactions are carried out instantly and within minutes it will appear on
    your Account Overview. </string>
    <string name="AccountManagementPersonal">Update your details </string>
    <string name="AccountManagementSecurity">Change Passcode</string>
    <string name="AccountManagementAccountName">Change Account name</string>
    <string name="AccountManagementBackground">Change Background</string>
    <string name="title_activity_network_error">NetworkErrorActivity</string>
    <string name="ReportLost">Lost/Stole</string>
    <string name="ReportIssue">Having an issue</string>
    <string name="UpdateYourDetailsTitle">Update your Personal Details</string>
    <string name="UpdateYourDetailsimportant">Customer\'s are advice to change their personal details using our Lloyd\'s App. Edit you details below and submit your request by clicking on the Update button.
    Please allow 48 hours for changes to take effect. </string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionTitle">Terms and Condition</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionA1">1.1 This document sets out the general conditions for our sterling bank accounts and related banking services for personal customers resident in the
    United Kingdom (‘UK’). These accounts and services may also have additional conditions (see condition 2 for more details). If we offer other services in the future, we will make it clear at the
    time if these general conditions will apply to them.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionA">Once you have registered, we can also provide Mobile Banking. This includes a range of text alert services
    where we send you text messages with information about your current accounts and Mobile Banking which allows you to access information on your
    accounts and give us certain instructions using your mobile phone.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionA2">1.2 You may not be eligible for all of our accounts or services or all the features they have – for example, we will not give you a Planned Overdraft if you
    are under 18. We may also limit the number of accounts or services you can hold with us.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionA3">1.3 An important part of our role as your bank is to provide you with services to help you manage your finances. We do not generally provide advice,
    but we can use information we have about you to suggest other services we think might interest you. To find out more about how we and other Lloyds Banking Group companies use your personal
    information, please read the section at the end of these terms and conditions headed ‘Important information about your personal information’. Please ask us if you have any questions about this
    agreement or any other matter by visiting one of our branches, calling us or writing to us.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionA2.1">2.1 This agreement for the above bank accounts and related banking services is made up of the ‘general conditions’ in this document and any ‘additional
    conditions’ we give you for these accounts or services. We will tell you if these general conditions apply when you take a new product or service from us.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionA2.2">2.2 If any additional condition conflicts with any general condition in this document, the additional condition will apply. For example a savings account may have different terms for working out or paying
    interest, so those terms will apply instead of the conflicting terms in these general conditions.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionB3.1">3.1 Our contact details are in the contact details section at the beginning of this document.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionB3.2">3.2 You can contact us and give us instructions in branch, through Telephone Banking, Internet Banking or Mobile Banking (once you have registered for them), or by using a card.
    Any instructions you give us are not effective until we actually receive them. You can usually use our Telephone, Internet and Mobile Banking services and Cashpoint machines at all times
    but occasionally repairs, updates and routine maintenance on our systems and those of our suppliers may mean that a particular service cannot be used for a short time (usually just minutes).</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionB3.3">3.3 We may contact you by post, telephone and electronically using the contact details you give us (including any electronic address that we
    agree with you will be used to send you electronic communications). When we use the words ‘electronic’ or ‘electronically’ in this agreement we mean any form of message made by any type of
    telecommunication, digital or IT device (including the internet, digital television, email and text message). You must tell us if your name or contact details change. If you do not tell us, we will go on
    using the details you last gave us, and we will not be responsible if we fail to contact you or if we send confidential information to the wrong address using out of date details. We will charge you our reasonable costs of finding you (or trying to find
    you) if your contact details are not up to date. </string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionB3.4">3.4 We may listen into or record any phone calls with you to check we have carried out your instructions correctly, to help improve our service, check that we comply with our regulatory obligations, and to
    help detect or prevent fraud or other crimes.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionB4.1">4.1 When we contact you or you contact us we need to check your identity before you can give us instructions or we can disclose or discuss confidential information about your accounts.
    For this reason:</string>
     <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionB4.1a">a.  you must sign instructions given on paper;</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionB4.1b">b.  when you are in a branch, we may ask you for identification; and</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionB4.1c">c.  if you are contacting us or giving us instructions by any other method (for example by using a card, Telephone Banking, Internet Banking or
    by Mobile Banking) you must do so using the ‘Security Details’ we have given to you or agreed with you personally.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionC5.1">5.1 General conditions about payments into your account.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionC5.1a">a.  In this condition we explain the timing of different types of payment into your account.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionC5.1b">b.  On some of our current accounts we offer instant cheque value, which means we will start paying you any interest straight away for the first
    £1,000 of cheques you pay in over the counter at one of our branches before the cut-off time on a working day. For amounts over £1,000 or where we do not offer instant cheque value. </string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionC5.1c">c.  if you are contacting us or giving us instructions by any other method (for example by using a card, Telephone Banking, Internet Banking or
    by Mobile Banking) you must do so using the ‘Security Details’ we have given to you or agreed with you personally.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionD6.1">6.1 If two or more of you are party to this agreement, the following terms apply:</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionD6.1a">a.  Any of you can give us instructions independently of the others on your joint accounts. This means any one of you can, for example, withdraw all or any money on an
    account without the knowledge of the others, close an account or end a service, ask for statements and correspondence to be given electronically alone or by paper too, and apply for overdrafts, cards and other services or different accounts with benefits packages which
    are covered by this agreement, and which are available on your joint accounts. We will not normally make enquiries about the purpose of any payment instruction or other instruction
    or confirm the instructions with the other joint customers. </string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionD6.1b">b.  Any one of you can replace an account or service with another account or service covered by these general conditions on behalf of all of you. </string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionD6.1c">c.  We may give any information about your joint account and the payments on it to any one of you, although you can ask us to send
    you separate current account statements if you live at different addresses. We can act on information about you which any of you gives us.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionMessageSectionD6.1d">c.  If any of you die, we can, but are not bound to, continue to act on the instructions of the remaining joint customers in relation to any joint accounts held by you, including allowing them
    to withdraw any or all money from the accounts and provide instructions relating to any services or benefits associated with the accounts.</string>
    <string name="TermsandConditionAddress">Lloyds Bank plc. Registered Office:\n
        25 Gresham Street, London EC2V 7HN.\n
        Registered in England and Wales no. 2065.\n
        Lloyds Bank plc is authorised by the Prudential\n
        Regulation Authority and regulated by the\n
        Financial Conduct Authority and the Prudential\n
        Regulation Authority under registration\n
        number 119278.\n
        \nInformation correct as at April 2014.</string>

    <string name="FAQSmessage" >Welcome to our help centre. Here you can find answers to out Frequently Asked Questions. If for any reason you couldn\'t find what you are looking for, then
    please do try and get in touch with us either via phone or email. </string>
    <string name="FAQQuestion1">How can I contact my local branch?</string>
    <string name="FAQAnswer1"> To contact us by phone, please call us on 0845 3 000 000 (calls may be recorded). Our UK-based advisers are able to answer a wide range of banking queries and are available 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. They are able to put you in touch with your local branch if required.</string>
    <string name="FAQQuestion2">I don\'t recognise a transaction on my account - what do I do?</string>
    <string name="FAQAnswer2">You can use our Fraud Detection feature we have introduced new to our app. Next to every transaction there is a question mark symbol next to it, if you believe that
    that transaction is not been made by you then click on the symbol and follow the wizard on the screen. </string>
    <string name="FAQQuestion3">Who can I contact if I have a query on my balance and transaction?</string>
    <string name="FAQAnswer3">If you want to talk to us about your balance or transactions, call Phonebank on 0845 3 000 000 or go to any Lloyds Bank branch. </string>
    <string name="FAQQuestion4">How do I transfer money to another person?</string>
    <string name="FAQAnswer4">If you\'re registered for Mobile Banking, you can transfer money between accounts and also make payments to pay a bill or another person through your phone, please do have a look on our
        Lloyds Banking Tour to familiarise your self with how to go about it.</string>
    <string name="FAQQuestion5">Can I change my Passcode?</string>
    <string name="FAQAnswer5">Yes you can, click on the Account Management option inside the Help Menu. This will take you to another window where you will have the option to change your Passcode. </string>
    <string name="ReportOnline">Report Online</string>
    <string name="LostorStoleTitle">Lost or stolen cards</string>
    <string name="LostorStoleMessage">If your Lloyds Bank credit or debit card has been lost or stolen you should report it immediately. You can report it through this app or by calling us.\n
    \nIf your Visa Debit Card is lost or stolen, we’ll cancel your old card and deliver a new one to you usually within 3-5 working days. If your card is declined, there are transactions that
    you don’t recognise or you need a new PIN, call us by clicking on the button below.</string>
    <string name="Reportlostorstoledownmessage">We guarantee to refund your money in the unlikely event you experience fraud with our Internet Banking service – as long as you’ve been careful, for example, by taking reasonable steps to keep your security information safe.</string>
    <string name="RportLostorStolelastMessage">We will trace your report and get in touch with you to inform the outcome. One of our member from the Fraud Department will be in touch with you and this usually happens
    within the 12 hour period that you have reported to us. </string>
    <string name="AboutUsLegal">Lloyds Bank plc is authorised by the Prudential Regulation Authority and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority and the Prudential Regulation Authority under registration number 119278. Authorisation can be checked on the Financial Services Register at www.fca.org.uk. Lloyds Bank plc is a member of the Financial Services Compensation Scheme and the Financial Ombudsman Service. We subscribe to the Lending Code; copies of the Code can be obtained from www.lendingstandardsboard.org.uk.\n
\nLloyds Bank plc Registered Office: 25 Gresham Street, London EC2V 7HN. Registered in England and Wales No. 2065.</string>
    <string name="AboutUsMessage">Be wary of suspicious calls, we\'ll never ask you to transfer money out of your account to another account for security purposes. </string>
    <string name="AboutUsChecklist">There are simple solutions you can put in place to keep you and your information safe online. Find out how you can:</string>
    <string name="AboutUsChecklistList1">Use anti-virus software</string>
    <string name="AboutUsChecklistList2">Prevent spam </string>
    <string name="AboutUsChecklistList3">Secure your wireless connection</string>
    <string name="AboutUsChecklistList4">Keep your operating system up to date</string>
    <string name="ManageStatementMessage">Make fast, easy transfers between Lloyds Bank accounts and easily access your credit card, current account and savings account statements online or either by paper statement. </string>
    <string name="ManageStatement1">Switch to paperless and receive your credit card, current account and savings statements safely and easily online. </string>
    <string name="ManageStatement2">Why get your statements online?</string>
    <string name="ManageStatement2a">You can safely access your account statements online.</string>
    <string name="ManageStatement2b">Easily search your account statements by date, amount or payment type.</string>
    <string name="HavinganIssueTItle">Having an issue</string>
    <string name="HavinganIssueMEssage">It is important to us to make sure that our customer\'s are getting a good service and that they are staying safe while using Mobile Banking with Lloyds Banking Group.
    f you been experiencing any sort of difficulties while using Lloyds mobile banking app please use this section of the app to get in touch with us. \n
    \nOne of our staff from the Customer Service will be in touch with you to resolve your issue, this doesn\'t take any more than 12 hour from when you have completed our online process. </string>
    <string-array name="havingissuecategory">
        <item>General Enquiries (colour, font size)</item>
        <item>Account Management</item>
        <item>Login</item>
        <item>Pay a contact</item>
        <item>Banking Facilities</item>
        <item>Transaction</item>
        <item>Budget</item>
        <item>Deals</item>
        <item>Tutorial Menu</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="OtherProductsMessage">We\’ll give you all the information you need to find your way around each section with images, tips and advices.</string>
    <string name="OtherPorductsMortgage">Whether you\'re buying your first home, looking for a better deal or simply want to know more about mortgages, we can help.\n
    \nOur mortgage basics guide covers what you will need to think about when looking for a home and applying for a mortgage;\n

 \n - Mortgage promise\n
- Moving costs\n
 - Property types\n
 - Valuation schemes\n
 - Repayment methods\n
 - Mortgage products\n
 - Legal work</string>
    <string name="OtherProductsMortgageinfo"><u>Find out more about Mortgages</u></string>
    <string name="OtherProductsCreditCardinfo"><u>Find out more about Credit Cards</u></string>
    <string name="OtherProductsCreditCardMessage">Managed properly, a credit card can be a safe and convenient way to pay for things – from a weekly shop to a summer holiday.\n
    \nBefore you apply\n
        \n - Check that you’re registered to vote
        \n - Make sure other accounts have your current address details
        \n - Have important personal details to hand
    </string>
    <string name="OtherProductsLoansinfo"><u>Find out more about Loans</u></string>
    <string name="OtherProductsLoansMesage">Used wisely, loans are a powerful financial tool that can help you get what you want out of life.\n
    \nOne of the best ways of comparing different loans of different interest rates and lengths is to look at the total amount repayable.
    This tells you, over the entire life of the loan, how much you will have to repay in total.\n
    \nIn summary, make sure you know the repayment terms of your loan before signing up and make sure you\’ll have enough income to make the repayments
        on time and without any worries.</string>
    <string name="OtherProductsInsuranceinfo"><u>Find out more about Insurance</u></string>
    <string name="OtherProductsInsuranceMessage">Get useful tips and help with understanding your insurance and protecting the things you care about.\n
    \n - Winter-proof your home\n
    - Protect your home against burglars\n
    - Find out what wear and tear means\n
    - Protect your home against floods</string>
    <string name="title_activity_budget_settings">BudgetSettings</string>
    <string name="FraudScrenMessage1">We guarantee to refund your money in the unlikely event you experience fraud with our Internet Banking service -
    as long as you’ve been careful, for example, by taking reasonable steps to keep your security information safe.</string>
    <string name="FraudScreenMessage1a">Keep your password secure and do not let anyone else make use of your security details</string>
    <string name="FraudScreenMessage1b">Do not let anyone watch you enter your security details</string>
    <string name="FraudScreenMessage1c">After each session make sure to log out off the system</string>
    <string name="FraudScreenMEssage"> With Lloyds Bank you have the confidence that shopping on the Internet is as safe and easy as shopping on the high street.
        That\'s because we promise you that whenever you use your Lloyds Bank credit or debit card to shop online, you\'ll be protected against fraud
</string>
    <string name="FraudScreenMEssage1">Whenever you buy goods or services online with participating retailers, Lloyds Bank ClickSafe® will give you extra protection against card crime.</string>



</resources>
